AoM Records 5593
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AoM Records
1936-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Academy of Management (AoM)
5593
68.61 cubic feet
68.6 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consist of letters, business records, membership records, publications and other routine documents.
2297032
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 20, 2019
Biographical / Historical
A professional association of academicians and practitioners in the field of business management and related disciplines. The Academy was founded in Chicago, Ill. in 1936 as "an organization of educators to advance the philosophy of management." The membership of the Academy, 5200 as of 1983, consists of faculty in accredited universities and colleges who teach management and "selected business executives who have made significant written contributions to the literature in the field of management and organization." The Academy holds an annual meeting, frequent regional meetings in the United States and several foreign countries, and publishes the ACADEMY OF MANAGEMENT JOURNAL and the ACADEMY OF MANAGEMENT REVIEW on a quarterly basis, as well as the proceedings of its annual meeting and several regional and professional division newsletters.
Scope and Contents
Consist of letters, business records, membership records, publications and other routine documents.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5607: Keppele Hall Papers 5593 AV: AoM Audio-Visual Material 5614: Feiss Company Records 5615: Sanford E. Thompson Papers 5618: Charles D. Wrege Research Papers Regarding History of Management
Arrangement
Series I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
Sub-Series A. GOVERNANCE DOCUMENTS Sub-Series B. ANNUAL MEETINGS Sub-Series C. Executive Officers Sub-Series D. Committee Records Sub-Series E. Regional Division Records Sub-Series F. Professional Division Records Sub-Series G. Financial Records Sub-Series H. Publications Award Files Sub-Series G. Miscellaneous
Series II. Publications
Sub-Series A. Correspondence Concerning Academy's Publications Sub-Series B. Publications (Journal, Review, Executive, Newsletter) and Miscellaneous
Series III. Miscellaneous
Industrial management -- United States; Management science -- Study and teaching -- United States; Management science.; Professional associations -- United States -- Administration; Trade and professional associations -- United States; Executives. Professional associations. United States.; United States. Economic conditions. 1945-. Addresses, essays, lectures.; Cannon, Warren; Dale, Ernest, 1917-1996; Davis, Keith, 1918-; Davis, Robert; Etzioni, Amitai; Glueck, William F.; Goetz, William; Gordon, Paul J.; Gore, George J.; Henderson, Robert D.; Hicks, Herbert G.; Hill, Walter A., 1946-; Jamison, Charles L. (Charles Laselle), 1885-; Le Breton, Preston P.; Litterer, Joseph August, 1926-; Mandeville, Merten Joseph, 1895-1976; Maytag, Fred; McFarland, Dalton E.; McGuire, Joseph William; Mee, John F. (John Franklin), 1908-1985; Pledger, Rosemary; Porter, Lyman W.; Reyer, Karl D. (Karl Dustin); Richards, Max De Voe, 1923-; Robb, Seward; Shulman, Daniel R.; Shulman, Ronald B.; Smiddy, Harold F., 1900-1978; Steiner, George Albert, 1912-; Summer, Charles Edgar; Taggart, Joseph; Terry, George Robert; Towle, Joseph W.; Vance, Stanley C.; Wolf, William B.; Academy of Management; American Management Association
2297032
- Series I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series A. GOVERNANCE DOCUMENTS
    - Sub-Series 1. Constitutions
      - Constitutional Revisions submitted by the Constitutional Revisions Committee, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Constitution, 1948-1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Academy of Management Constitution (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Constitution, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Constitution, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Constitution, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Constitution, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        Scope and Contents
        Includes proposed changes
      - Constitution, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Constitution, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Constitution, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Constitution, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Constitution, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Constitution (Box 1, Folder 13)
        undated
      - Constitution (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Constitution (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - By-Laws & Appendices (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1948-1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        Correspondence, 6/48 - 11/62
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        with proposed amendment
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        Correspondence, 11/62 - 3/67
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Correspondence, 3/67 - 5/67
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        Correspondence, 7/67 - 9/67
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Correspondence, 10/67 - 12/71
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        Governance Documents, Correspondence RE: Constitutional Changes, Includes Constitutional Drafts
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        Correspondence, 10/74 - 2/75
      - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 14)
        Proposed Changes
      - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        Board of Governors' Proposed Changes
      - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 18)
        Changes, undated
      - Constitution, General (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Sub-Series 2. Board of Governors
      Includes minutes, correspondence, etc. in chronological order
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
        12/66 - 5/69
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
        5/69 - 12/69
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        12/69 - 3/70
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        3/70 - 11/70
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        12/70 - 4/71
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        4/71 - 11/71
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        12/71 - 11/73
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        3/74 - 9/75
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Board of Governors, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Board of Governors, Minutes of Meeting, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
        27-Dec-47
      - Board of Governors, Minutes of Meeting, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Board of Governors, Minutes of Meeting, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Board of Governors, Minutes of Meeting, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Board of Governors, Minutes of Meeting, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Board of Governors, Minutes of Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Board of Governors, General (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Board of Governors, Agendas, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        Program, Agenda, Minutes, November 30 - December 1, 1973
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        December 6 - 7, 1974
      - Board of Governors, Minutes of Business Meetings, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Scottsdale, AZ, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
        Agenda and Program, May 3 - 4, 1974
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Seattle, WA, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
        Agenda and Program, August 12, 1974
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        Correspondence with Orlando Hyatt House for August '77 Meeting
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        Correspondence, etc., August 17 - 20, 1975
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, San Francisco, CA, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        Minutes, May 8, 1976
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Kissimmee, FL, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
        Correspondence and Minutes, November 21, 1975
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Kansas City, MO, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
        10-Aug-76
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Kansas City, MO, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
        11-Aug-76
      - Board of Governors, Business Meeting, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        Minutes, August 14, 1976
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
        Program and Agenda, November 20, 1976
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
        Agenda, November 20, 1976
      - Board of Governors, Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
        Agenda, Miscellaneous Correspondence and Documents pertaining to said meeting, November 1976
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
        Correspondence and Reports, For 1976
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        Minutes, Milwaukee, WI. April 1977
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Milwaukee, WI, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        Program and Agenda, April 29 - 30, 1977
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
        Agenda of Meeting, 4/77
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        Agenda of Meeting, 8/77
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Kissimmee, FL, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        Minutes, August 1977
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Kissimmee, FL, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
        Agenda and Program, August 13, 1977
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, San Francisco, CA, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
        Minutes, Program and Agenda, December 2, 1977
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, New York City, NY, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
        Correspondence and Reports, April 28 - 30, 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, New York City, NY, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
        Miscellaneous, April 29 - 30, 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, New York City, NY, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3a)
        Agenda
      - Board of Governors, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        Agenda of Meeting, 4/78
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, San Francisco, CA, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        Agenda, August 8 - 9, 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, San Francisco, CA, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
        Agenda, Minutes and Program, August 8 - 9, 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
        Agenda and Minutes
      - Board of Governors, Fall Meeting, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Board of Governors, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
        Agenda of Meeting, 8/78
      - Board of Governors, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
        Agenda of Meeting, Fall 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
        Board of Governors, Meeting
      - Board of Governors, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        Correspondence RE: Membership
      - Board of Governors, Board Meeting (Box 8, Folder 2)
        (Correspondence?) San Francisco, CA. August 8 - 9, 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
        Minutes, New York City, NY
      - Board of Governors, Meeting (Box 8, Folder 4)
        New York City, April 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, San Francisco, CA (Box 8, Folder 5)
        Minutes, August 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting (Box 8, Folder 6)
        Report of Site Selection Committee, Fall 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Atlanta, GA (Box 8, Folder 7)
        Minutes November 1978
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
        Correspondence and Reports
      - Board of Governors (Box 8, Folder 9)
        Agenda for Spring Meeting and Correspondence RE: Same, Denver, CO, May 5, 1979
      - Board of Governors, Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA (Box 8, Folder 10)
        Aug-79
      - Board of Governors Meeting, New Orleans (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Board of Governors, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
        Fall Meeting, Agenda
      - Board of Governors, Meeting (Box 8, Folder 13)
        Agenda, November 30 -December 1, 1979
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Detroit, MI (Box 8, Folder 14)
        Correspondence and Reports, November 30 - December 1, 1979
      - Board of Governors, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
        Correspondence RE: Annual Meeting
      - Board of Governors, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Board of Governors, Committee Reports, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Board of Governors, Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
        Agenda and Miscellaneous Correspondence, August 1979
      - Board of Governors, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
        Spring Meeting Agenda
      - Board of Governors, Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Board of Governors, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
        Correspondence RE: Spring Meeting Denver, CO. May 5, 1979
      - Board of Governors, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
        Agenda for Meeting, Spring 1979
      - Board of Governors, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
        Interim Report on the 1979 Proceedings
      - Board of Governors, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
        Report of David Van Fleet, Academy of Management Policies and Procedures Manual
      - Board of Governors Files, Meeting, Atlanta, GA, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Board of Governors, Meetings, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
        Minutes, April 1980
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Detroit, MI, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
        Aug-80
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Las Vegas, NV, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
        Correspondence, April 25 - 26, 1980
      - Academy Board of Governors, Meeting, Detroit, MI, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
        Correspondence, Reports, etc., August 9 - 13, 1980
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Las Vegas, NV, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 14)
        Correspondence, Reports, etc., December 12 - 14, 1980
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Las Vegas, NV, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
        Agenda December 1980
      - Board of Governors, Meetings, New York City, NY, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
        Correspondence, Reports, etc. April 24 - 26, 1981
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, Detroit, MI, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, NY Hilton, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
        Agenda, April 25, 1981
      - Board of Governors, Meeting, San Diego, CA, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
        Agenda August 1 - 2, 1981
      - Board of Governors, Task Force I Report (Hall), 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Board of Governors, Task Force I Report (Hall), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Board of Governors, Task Force III, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Board of Governors, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Robert Duncan, VP, Board of Governors, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
        Correspondence pertaining to Annual Meeting, San Diego, CA
  - Sub-Series B. ANNUAL MEETINGS
    - Annual Meeting, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      (includes proceedings) includes correspondence of C.I. Jamison - one of the Academy of Management's founders, Ann Arbor, MI
    - Annual Meeting, Philadelphia, New Orleans, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Minutes and Attendants
    - Annual Meetings, 1941-1947 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      includes correspondence with C. I. Jamison and Ralph C. Davis, founders of the Academy, New York, Chicago
    - Annual Meeting, Cleveland, OH, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Minutes and Election Materials, December 1948
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Cleveland, OH, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Dec-48
    - Annual Meeting, Cleveland, OH, Announcement, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      (includes proceedings) includes correspondence with Ralph Davis (Ohio Univ. Professor), one of the founders of the Academy, includes correspondence concerning revitalization of Academy after the War (WWII). Also, correspondence with John F. Mee (Indiana U
    - Annual Meeting, 4th Annual Conference, Attendance List (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, New York City, NY, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Agenda and Address, December 30, 1949
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings of the Academy of Management, New York City, NY, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      30-Dec-49
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, New York City, NY, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting, Chicago, IL, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Minutes, Officers
    - Annual Meeting, Cambridge, MA, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Includes Proceedings, Chicago, Papers: Management Training Program (Fred Maytag), Management Problems Post War Economics (R. C. Davis)
    - Annual Meeting, Materials for Annual Meeting, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Includes Proceedings, Washington, D.C., Address: Samuel Burke (General Foods Corporation, Director, I.R.) in Principles of Organization
    - Annual Meeting, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Outline of Address by Ralph C. Davis, The Capital - Turnover Factor in Long-Range Planning for Business Growth
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Detroit, MI, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Includes "The Capital-Turnover Factor in Long-Range Planning for Business Growth," a paper by Ralph C. Davis - co-founder of the Academy of Management, Detroit
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Papers, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Jackson Martindell, Leadership; John F. Mee, Management in Academia; John G. Staiger, Management Philosophy in American Motors Corp
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, New York, Addresses, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      John H. Hoagland, Management Before Taylor; F. H. Brown, Chrysler Motor- Management; R. O. Ferguson, Quantitative Research; W. Van Alan Clark, Management Education at MIT; Charles E. Sommer, Adm. Curricula at various Univ
    - Annual Meetings, Proceedings, New York City, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meetings, Proceedings, New York City, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Correspondence and Materials for Meeting
    - Annual Meeting, Cleveland, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Addresses, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      C. I. Keelan, EDP Systems; C. E. Summer, Effective Administration; Harold Koontz, Planning and Control. Panel discussion case studies in teaching management principles - R. Shuman, R. C. Davis, et al
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Philadelphia, Panel Discussion, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Executive Development Programs, Use of Business Environment in Teaching
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 5)
      William E. Goetz (MIT), Joseph W. Towle
    - Annual Meeting, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Correspondence of Joe Towle, Secretary-Treasurer, Chicago, with various members. RE: Org. Annual Meeting - Format, etc.
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Chicago, Addresses, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Charles Haffner (R.R. Donnelly & Sons). Orgs. and Policy; Albert Schreiber (Univ. of Washington) Executive Decision Making-Game Theory
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Chicago, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Washington, D.C., Addresses, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Harold Smiddy (General Electric, VP), Research and Management. Panel - Research and Management in Academia, Scientific Management, also: Labor Management Research; Government Research; Research in Org. and Authority
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Washington, D.C, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, St. Louis, MO, Addresses, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      David Moore, Management Philosophy; Albert Rubenstein, Org. Research; William Schlender, Org. Theory-Concepts; Kalman Cohen, Computer Simulation
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, St. Louis, MO, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting, St. Louis, MO, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      includes correspondence of Joe Towle, George Terry, President, Vice-President of the Academy, St. Louis, MO, RE: Format of Meeting
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, New York Addresses, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Thomas Carroll, Management Education; William Brady, Management International Business; William Mitchell, Management Education; Bernard Baum, Bureaucratic Authority Centralization; Clarence Walton, Business and Social System. Panels: Information explosion
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, New York, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting, New York, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Annual Meeting, New York, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      includes correspondence of Keith Davis, Secretary-Treasurer of the Academy, New York
    - Annual Meeting, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, New York, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Pittsburgh, PA, Addresses, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Behavioral Science/Management Curricula, staffing, management training, compensation, audits, policy studies, planning, org. control, systems theory, games. Pres. address: Harold F. Smiddy, Management Theory
    - Annual Meeting, Pittsburgh, PA, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Program of the Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      December 27 - 28, 1963
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Boston, MA Addresses, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Bureaucracy (leadership-deal making), business education, personnel management (Dale Yoder), psychological applications on academia, manpower, management information systems, network planning, leadership
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Boston, MA, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 24th Annual Meeting, Chicago, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Program, December 1964
    - 24th Annual Meeting, Chicago, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Papers and Correspondence
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, Chicago, "Evolving Concepts in Management" Addresses (Box 15, Folder 12)
      public role-management, social roles of corp-org objectives, structure of management processes, info. technology on org., management control theory, employee appeal systems, production management
    - Annual Meeting, List of Participants, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Dec-65
    - Annual Meeting, New York, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting, Proceedings, San Francisco, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 15)